Hello.
مرحبًا.
Welcome to our first lesson in English listening practice.
مرحبًا بكم في درسنا الأول في ممارسة الاستماع باللغة الإنجليزية.
Let's start today's lesson.
لنبدأ درس اليوم.
This lesson is very useful.
هذا الدرس مفيد جدًا.
We're going to use important
سنستخدم عبارات مهمة
English phrases for the airport.
عبارات إنجليزية للمطار.
Traveling can be stressful.
السفر يمكن أن يكون مرهقًا.
I understand that.
أفهم ذلك.
But if you know the common questions
لكن إذا كنت تعرف الأسئلة الشائعة
and phrases people use at the airport,
والعبارات التي يستخدمها الناس في المطار،
and if you know what to listen for,
وإذا كنت تعرف ما الذي تستمع إليه،
your trip will feel much easier
ستشعر أن رحلتك أصبحت أسهل بكثير
and less stressful.
وأقل توترًا.
In this video, I will guide you.
في هذا الفيديو، سأرشدك.
I will speak slowly and clearly.
سأتحدث ببطء ووضوح.
Please listen carefully.
يرجى الاستماع بعناية.
If you want, you can repeat after me.
إذا أردت، يمكنك التكرار بعدي.
This will help improve both your listening
هذا سيساعد في تحسين مهارات الاستماع
skills and speaking skills.
ومهارات التحدث.
Are you ready?
هل أنت مستعد؟
Let's begin.
لنبدأ.
Today I want to tell you
اليوم أريد أن أخبركم
a short, simple story.
قصة قصيرة وبسيطة.
I am going on a trip.
أنا ذاهب في رحلة.
I am traveling to another country.
أنا مسافر إلى دولة أخرى.
It's early in the morning.
إنه صباح باكر.